Zombieland: Double Tap is a horror, comedy film directed by Ruben Fleischer.
Columbus, Tallahassee, Wichita, and Little Rock move to the American heartland as they face off against
evolved zombies, fellow survivors, and the growing pains of the snarky makeshift family.
Tallahassee, played by Woody Harrelson.
Columbus, played by Jesse Eisenberg.
Wichita, played by Emma Stone.
Little Rock, played by Abigail Breslin.
Madison, played by Zoey Deutch.
Berkeley, played by Avan Jogia.
Zombieland: Double Tap is a 2019 American post-apocalyptic zombie comedy film directed by
Ruben Fleischer and written by Rhett Reese, Paul Wernick, and David Callaham.
The sequel to Zombieland (2009), it stars an ensemble cast including Woody Harrelson, Jesse Eisenberg, Abigail Breslin, Emma
Stone (all reprising their roles), Rosario Dawson, Zoey Deutch, Avan Jogia, Luke Wilson, and Thomas Middleditch.
In the sequel, Tallahassee (Harrelson), Columbus (Eisenberg), and Wichita (Stone) face evolved zombies and encounter
other survivors as they travel from the White House to Graceland to search for Little Rock (Breslin).
A sequel to the original film began development in November 2009, with the
returns of Reese, Wernick, Fleischer and the main cast planned.
It soon faced several delays, and the writers instead wrote a Zombieland television pilot in 2013
featuring a new cast, which ultimately failed in being ordered for a series release.
Development for the sequel film was revived in February 2016, the screenplay was
completed in March 2017, and the film was confirmed in July 2018.
The rest of the cast was rounded out under a year later, and principal photography began in
January 2019 and concluded that March, with filming primarily taking place in Atlanta.
Zombieland: Double Tap premiered in Los Angeles on October 10, 2019, was theatrically
released in the United States on October 18, by Sony Pictures Releasing.
It received mostly positive reviews from critics, who found it to be a worthwhile successor to the
original and praised the cast performances (particularly those of Stone and Deutch).
The film grossed $125 million worldwide, surpassing its predecessor.
The film explores themes of marriage proposal, the
white house, gore, road trip, sequel.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.